Guide to the Theatre and Dance Department records, 1937-2011 RG0084
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Videotapes, 1968-2008; RG0084 Series 5 (Film can 13, Film can 11, Box 1, Film can 12, Film can 16, Film can 17, Film can 14, Film can 15, Box 2)
  - "Blithe Spirit", 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Noel Coward (Playwright); Bill Largess (Director); David Robinson (Scenic Design); Stephen S. Gray (Lighting Design); Kristina Huie (Costume Design); Maya RobinsonMaggie ContrerasSimone Zvi, Leigh-Erin Balmer, Dan Berman, Russull Feder, Darby o"Donnell, Cristin Guinana-Wiley, Emily Beaton, Nate Garner, Carl F. Gudenius, Frank Page, Anna Derryberry, Meghan MacFarland, Abiail Marks, Allison Curtis, Runjit Chandra, Simone Zvi, Shendrina Alexander, William Pucilowsky, Amanda Edgerton, Jasmine Briggs, Elizabeth Groth, Natasha Pavlobich,Leslie B Jacobson, Marky Buckley, Nate Garner, Carl Gudenius, Framji Minwalla, William Pucilowsky, Bradley Sabelli, Dana Tai Soon Burgess, Maida Withers, Alan Wade, Ken Clark, Jennifer Gerstein, Frank Page, Holly Thomas, Kelsey Banyan, Emily Beaton, William Chen, Amanda Curtis, Erin Fitzgerald, Crystal Flaherty, Jessica Geisinger, Phillip Grosser, Matt Helman, Christ Hwalek, Matthew Johnson, Jessica Strile, Jennifer Gerstein,
  - "The Apple Tree", 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Jerry Bock and Sheldon Harnick (Playwright); Leslie Jacobson (Director); James Wolk (Scenic Design); Carl F. Gudenius (Lighting Design); Denise Umland (Costume Design); Mary BuckleyDan BermanAlice MikolajewskiAngela AfentakisLia LaCour, Blake Ross, Abigail Marks, Evan Shyer, Maggie Contreras, Jeff Consoletti, Joseph Dietrich, Jessie Familetti, Zack Colonna, Meredith Pryce, Zach Borichevsky, Jeff Stern, Kate Bolduan,Stephanie Glassman, Medora Sheehan, Lyndsey Munter, Michael McLaughlin, Allison Curtis, Janet Bowler, Anna Derryberry, Allison Mazer, John Kearns, Dan Berman, William Pucilowsky, Elizabeth Groth, Kristina Huie, Jennifer GersteinLeslie B. Jacobson, Mary Buckley, Nate Garner, Carl Gudenius, Framji Minwalla, William Pucilowsky, Gradley Sabelli, Dana Tai Soon Burgess, Madia Withers, Alan Wade, Ken Clark, Jennifer Gerstein, Frank PageAlice Mikolajewski, Crystal Hahn, Scott Bender, Jocelyn Pleasant
  - "Danceworks", 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Dana Tai Soon Burgess (Director); Maja E White (Lighting Design); Amanda Edgerton and Ellen Warner (Costume Designers); Nicholette Routhier, Kristy Shimabukuro, Tommy Parlon, Maida Withers, Mary Tisa, Anthony Gongora, Jennifer NugnetMeggie Baker, Cathryn PaineElizabeth Berk, Carolyn Craig, Jessica Gohs, Michael Gonene, Matthew Krell, Rebecca Lubart, Kendall Mrano, Polly Thibodeau, Amberlee Woods, Aliza Rudavsky, Chirstin Goelz, Pilar del Mazo, Lara Malakoff, Juliana Mascielli, Mollie Straff, Talia MamoneWilliam Pucilowsky, Krstina Hie, Stephen Gray, Jasmine Briggs, Amanda Edgerton, Elizabeth Groth, Natasha Pavlovich, Holly Thomas, Mary Lane, Samantha Schoenholtz, Christina Conley, Marcia Elena LoMonaco, Carrie Kerstein, Aliza Rudavsky, Jennifer GersteinSamantha Schoenholtz, Liz Denniston, Kati Chupasko, Jennifer Caulk, Sarah Halzack, Rebecca Lubart, Natalie Shriber, JJ Kovacevich, Mary Lane, Susanna Brown, Wendell Cooper, Natalie Shriber, Christina Conley, Nicholette Routhier, Kristy Shimabukuro, M Tisa
  - "The Winter's Tale", 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    William Shakespeare (Playwright); Alan Wade (Director); Carl F. Gudenius (Scenic Design); Carl F. Gudenius (Lighting Design); Esther Van Eek (Costume Design); Ryan DavidStephanie FreyerMaragret Artz, Megan McGrath, Jordan Siegel, Abigail Marks, Michelle Roberts, Kate Guesman, Rebecca Chodroff, Kelly McPhillips, Patrice Langue, Adam Gutbezahl, Ryan McGlone, Benjamin Trey Gibson, Christopher Hall, Matt Mezzacappa, Andrew DarceyAndrew Karlin, Jesse Guyer, Arielle Kahaner, Eugene Romero, Matt Mezzacappa, William Pcilowsky, Erin McAuliffLeslie B Jacobson, Mary Buckley, Dana Tai Soon Gurgess, Nate Garner, Carl Gudenius, William Pucilowsky, Bradley Sabelli, Maida Withers, Alan Wade, Marjorie Coleman, Andrew Kariln, Melissa NilssonAdam Gerber, Daniel Kenner, Jimmu Morgan, Eli Wiener
  - "H.M.S. Pinafore", 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Gilbert and Sullivan (Playwright); Leslie Jacobson (Director); Paul Gracza, Catherine Pickar, Ron Howard, Steve Shankroff, Lynn Kappenberger, Janet Thomason (Band); Bradley W. Sabelli (Scenic Design);Paul F. DempseyD.C.Recreation DepartmentSandra KammannCatherine Pickar (Music Advisor)Erik ComstockLisa A. OstrichM.Mills, T.Campbell, F.Ganzalez, C.Howe, L.Luxemburg, L.Zarowin, Jill Wendroff, L.Mufson, Linda Russano, E. Pierotti, V. McKernan, N.Ingvarsson, S.Landess, Lisa Witlin, B.Zirl, J.Rogers, Sally Bolger, Frank Deal, Tyler Young, Bonnie Kaplan, Marita NickensCindy Zrezel ASM, J.Steinberg, Rob Steinberg, P.Dempsey, C.Fishman, J.Rosenthal, B.Thomas, Esther Cohen, E. Peirotti, J. Bryer, R.Levine, Tyler Young, B.Zirl, E. Wolf, Curtis Jeffries, Biff Harte, Curtis Smith, Peter Adams, L. Mufson, Shelley Simon
  - "Crimes of the Heart", 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Beth Henley (Playwright); Nathan Garner (Director); Sheila Treanor (Scenic Design); Bil Joseph (Lighting Design); Susan Chiang (Costume Design); Todd Musser (PROPS)Lori AdlerChristopher G. Adams, Robert D. Cohen, Miriam Ervin, Katherine Jane Petrov, Anne Porterfield, Cheryl Smith. CREW:Alison Sandler, Matt Levin, Joe Kronk, Andrew Gorenstein, Andrea Perl, Wendy Bingman, Emily Lind, Gabrielle KasselValerie Gramling ASM, Rose Parent, Jocelyn Kuba, Michelle Shapiro, Susan Roman, Georgette Ryan, Lisa Cohen, Robert Bell, Audra Winter, James France, Cari Dick, Howard T. Dodd, Vania Deliyianni, Amy Chauken, Rob Feinblatt, A.Clotworthy, A.Bethea, J.Morris
  - "Steel Magnolias", 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Scott French and Cheryl Smith (Directors)
  - "Condor Qatay", 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Catherine Allen and Nathan Garner (Playwrights and Directors); Thora S.R. Colot (Scenic Design); Jonathan Blandin (Lighting Design); Kristin Celeste Kidd (Costume Design); Kim Deane - Properties DesignerJean LaFauciJenna Jones, Melissa Foulger, Jen Deitch, Deirdre Butler, Jonathan Holub, Ron Johnson, Nick Grace, Amy Wiese, Noel True, Brian Coleman, Mark Silver, Kelly BarnettASMs Jen Broadbent, Amy Renshaw. Jeff Fischer, assis props. Gena Farrington, Assis Scene Des. Assis costumer, Kellie Owens. cost crew: Tim Evans, Joanna Goode. Rachel Leslie ME. PR:Ellen Carroll, Angela Lauria. Rachel Flehinger, house. Veronica MorrisonPT: Nncy Sedgwick, Natalie M. Smith. Staff: Judy Annis, Thomas Fiocchi, Sara Hawes. GTAs Keith Costa, Heidi Geier, Kristin Kidd, David SmithThora S.R. Colot, Scene Design. Jonathan Blandin, Light Design.
  - "Moon Over the Brewery", 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Bruce Graham (Playwright); Nathan Garner (Director); James Wolk (Scenic Design); Carl F. Gudenius (Lighting Design); William Pucilowsky (Costume Design); James Kline (SOUND), Michael Pemberton, Alissa Rosen, Dariush Kashani, Scott French, Jennifer Carpiniello, Melissa Foulger ASM, V.Deliyianni, D.Hatcher, T.Evans, L.Shanoman, Greta Mandry, A.Copeland, Amy wiese, H.Kuukka, Frank Demes (Paintings), Grethen Wirth, Lorene Starcevich, Jessica Southwick Maureen herman, Kim Deans, Guri E. Maxwell, Sue Tanya HenryJames Wolk, Scene Design
  - "Mother Courage and Her Children", 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Bertolt Brecht (Playwright); Nathan Garner (Director); Barbara Brennan(Scenic Design); Rob Books (Lighting Design); Kate Turner-Walker (Costume Design); David GhatenLaura MannClaudia Alick,Ann Carr,candice Cook,Jenna Helwig,Kerry Washington,Jessica Chadwell,Laura Chares,Ali Foster,Rana Kay,Layra Mann,Julie Ott,Heather Wiser,Joseph Rogers,Ben Rubin,Michael Weitz,Andre Kozma,Troy Miller,Jose Gregory,Luke Enos,Cody Landis and....Mark Silver,William Pucilowsky,Thomas B. Fiocchi,Carl F. Gudenius,Marjorie Mills,Yuichi Nakajima,Jen Broadbent, Heather Pagella,Brian Coleman,Herschel BleefeldCAST:James Manfredi,Chris Hahn,Erik Kasik
  - "Waiting for Marge", 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Nick Mathwick (Playwright); Nathan Garner (Director); w/Smallbeer Theatre; memorial for NickSteve LeBlanc and Thomas B. Fiocci (Lighting Design); Robin Lyttle (Costume Design); Lynnie RaybuckJim Kline (SOUND)Alexandra CopelandJeremy Klavens, Adrian Bethea, Andy Shreeman, Alissa Rosen, Dariush KashaniScott French, Erin Stryker, S.Chiang, D.Hatcher, T.Evans, Lucy Shanoman, Margarete Mandy, Annette Smith, Leyla Keough, Jennifer Green, Kelly KernLynnie Raybuck, Costume Design;Steve LeBlanc, Scene Design;Robin Lyttle, Light Design
  - "Hay Fever", 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Noel Coward (Playwright); Nathan Garner (Director); Carl F. Gudenius (Scenic Design); Robert Books (Lighting Design); Kellie Owens (Costume Design); Mark SilverMark Silver, Carole Stover, John Degen, Maura Miller, Brian Coleman, Kristiana Knight, Alan Goy, Kerry Washington, Michael Laurino, Rachel Flehinger, Carl Gudenius, Thomas Fiocchi, Jenna Jones, Elyas Khawarzad, William Pucilowsky, Kellie Owens, Claudia Alick, Joe Blye, Tim Evans, Heather Lepp, Maria Serrano, Hugo Vaszuez, Charlotte Brenneman, Elizabeth Young, Randy Bomze, Joe Pouliot, Veronica MorrisonJudy Annis, Verna StederCarole Stover, John Degen
  - "The Me Nobody Knows", 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Livingston and Schapiro (Playwright); Muriel Von Villas (Director); Music by Friedman and Holt. based on the book ed by Joseph and an idea by Schapiro. Additional lyrics by Shapiro. Arrangements and orch by FriedmanDavid SmithKim DeaneAlicia S. FansmithJenefer DaviesFrank ConlonErika GrumetRachel Leslie, Kristiana Knight, Matt Bray, Ruth Jimenez, Joseph Panepinto, Jennifer Allegra, Candace Clark, Keith Pettigrew, Matt Wolf, Jonathan Leacock, Chritian Lilley, Karin Weinberg. Musicians Frank Conlon (keyb), Mark Carvallo (Bass), Brian WallaceASMs Deborah Fleming, Maura McKenna. Chris Hays, props. Kristin Kidd Costumer. assist cost, Kellie Owens. cost crew, Tim Evans, Joanna Goode. Michael Ruccolo, ME. Audra Polk, AME. Ellen Carroll, BO. Veronica Morrison, grafics. Ken Cobb, photo.
  - "Arcadia", 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Tom Stoppard (Playwright); N Garner and J. Ott (Director); Carl F. Gudenius (Scenic Design); Carl F. Gudenius (Lighting Design); Kate Turner-Walker (Costume Design); Laura Parris (waltz) Nick Johanson (sound)Ali FosterJanine Barris-Gerstl, John Tarleton, Julie Ott, Craig Geiling, Iwonka Swenson, Bonnie Waggoner, Jose Gregory, Fayth preyer, David Lipsitt, Mariah Sussman, Sean Abbott, Andrew MalowitzJ. Mann, F. Page, E. Miller, T. Koss, E. Wilhelm-Hilkey, J. Chadwell, J. Stewert, D. Schwatrz
  - "Dangerous Liaisons", 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Christopher Hampton (Playwright); Alan Wade (Director); Naoko Saga (Scenic Design); Maja White (Lighting Design); William Pucilowsky (Costume Design); Maya RobinsonFight Direction, Charles Conwell, Amanda Rosengberg, Russell Feder, Leigh-Erin Balmer, Julie Griffith, Meghan Locker, Matt Gula, Jared Mercier, Jenny Towns, Anna Meyer, Paul Kendrick, Dan Berman, Jeremy Furhman, John Kearns, Michael Lutton
  - "End of the World", 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Arthur Kopit (Playwright); Nathan Garner and William Balling (Directors, Lighting, and Scenic Design); The company/Ferhan Kiper (Costume Design); Nancy WygmansJack Sanderson, Roger Howarth, David J. Campbell, Ferhan Kiper, Beth Joy Witorsch, Mark S. Katic, Keven P. Keaveney, G.J.Stewart Walker, Gage Johnston, Jill Brewer, Rachel Milner, Cheryl Smith, Jeri Lyn Haiduk, Caryn Berla, Kevin C. PickneyDavid J. Campbell, Cheryl Smith, E.Hagenbarth, T.Sikorski, Nancy Schwalb, A. Moskowitz, andy Lottman, Wil McCarter, C.Orkild, C.DePalma, Julie Garbus, Caryn Beria, Dawn Pardo, Hannan Askala, Peter Madden, Bruce Burstein, Tod Gomer, Q.Gravatt, M.Schultz
  - "And They Stopped The Show", 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Leslie B. Jacobson (Playwright); Leslie B. Jacobson (Director); Barbara BrennanCarl (Costume Design); GudeniusKellie K. OwensRandi MearesJohn Anthony WardMark SilverClaudia Alick, Giancarlo Bacigalupo, Chris Bender, Veronica Byam, Jessica Chadwell, Kris Chruch, Christopher Hahn, Stephen Hellman, Maher Jafari, Ruth Jimenez, ALejo Jumat, Jean LaFauci, Michael Laurino, Jonathan Leacock, Renee Moskowitz, Mandy Rives, William Pucilowsky, Carl Gudenius, Thomas Fiocchi, Heather Wiser, Chris Bender, Jean LaFauci, Jennifer Deitch, Herschel Bleefield, Kellie Owens, Claudia Alick, Tim Evans, Heather Lepp, Students of TRDA 130-136, Elizabeth Young, Melissa Weiner, Chris HahnLeslie B. Jacobson, Judy Annis, Thomas Fiocchi, Shelley HoweKerry Washington, Teshina Wilson, Karin Weinberg, Judy Annis, Randy Bomze, Joe Pouliot, Verna Steder, Veronica Morrison
  - "As You Like It", 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Shakespeare (Playwright); Alan Wade (Director); Rob Books (Scenic Design); Rob Books (Lighting Design); Kate Turner-Walker (Costume Design); Gilbert NashJordanna L'esperanceDramaturge:Michael WeitzAnthony DiTannaJenifer BroadbentErik Kasik,David Lipsitt,Robert Dodd,Gilbert Nash,Wade Hancock,Cody Landiss,Sean Abbott,Michael Weitz,Claudia Alick,Brian Coleman,Zachary Kaplan,Luke Enos,Elyas Khawarzad,Herschel Bleefeld,Jonathan Leacock,Nat Rawson,Tony Delgado,Troy Miller,Colleen BerryWilliam Pucilowsky,Carl F. Gudenius,Thomas B. Fiocchi,Maura Miller,Chris Hahn,Sarah Ries,Claudia Alick,Tim Evans,Jessica Chadwell,Melissa Costello,David Ghatan,Heather Nathanson,Melissa Weiner,Judy Annis,Rachel Whisenant,Joe Pouliot,Kirsten Yauch...CAST:Meg Sullivan,Rana Kay,Julie White,Cate Brewer,Anthony DiTanna,Laura Parris MUSICIANS:Anthony DiTanna,Daniel Reed,Kirsten Xanthippe CREW:Veronica Morrison, Ashton Alvis
  - "The Marriage of Bette and Boo", 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Christopher Durang (Playwright); Alan Wade (Director); Rob Brooks (Scenic Design); James Misenheimer (Lighting Design); Maria Serrano (Costume Design); Chris HaysSound Designer-Chris HaysComposer-Richard PeaslerJenna JonesColleen Berry, Jenna Helwig, Toby Bordelon, Rachel Flehinger, Laura Becker, Eric Kasik, Ptolemy Slocum, Andrea Miles, Luke Enos, Brian ColemanWilliam Pucilowsky,Carl F. Gudenius,Thomas B.Fiocchi,Laura Mann,Jen Broadbent,Michael Weitz,Kellie Owens,Claudia Alick,Tim Evans,Heather Lepp,Jennifer Deitch,Amy Renshaw,Chris Hahn,Melissa Weiner,Judy Annis,Randy Bomze,Joe Pouliot,and Verna StederJudy Annis, Thomas Fiocchi, Shelly Howes, Robert Brooks, Barbara Brennan, Kellie OwensVeronica MorrisonSara A. Wagner-Dramaturg
  - "Dancing at Lughnasa", 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Brian Friel (Playwright); Marian DiJulio (Director); James Mesenheimer (Scenic Design); Barbara Brennan (Lighting Design); William Pucilowsky (Costume Design); Nancy Diers JohnsonRob MilburnSOUND: Rob MilburnJenifer BroadbentLuke Enos, Ashley Fleming, Candice Cook, Sara Wagner, Laura Mann, Ann Carr, Cody Landis, Jared PetersonCladia Alick ASM, Len Semon ASM, Chris Hahn PROPS, Dawn Schmidt, Kellie Owens, Claudia Alick, Joe Blye, Tim Evans, Maria Serrano, Hugo Vasquez, Mark Silver, Jenna Jones, Yuichi Nakajima ME, Melissa Weiner, Randy Bomze, Joe PouliotPOSTER DESIGN: Veronica Morrison, Carl Gudenius, Thomas Fiocchi, Len Semon, Dawn Schmidt, William Pucilowsky, Kellie Owens, Judy Annis, Verna StederMarian DiJulio
  - "Dance Works Fall 2001", 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - "The Memorandum", 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Vaclav Havel (Playwright); Alan Wade (Director); Jason Mann (Costume Design); Lynn JoslinWilliam PucilowskyJulie S. StrachanZach Kaplan, Anne Kramlinger, Sabrina Hyman, Christopher Hahn, Alysha Kahn, Mariah Sussman, Erica Pitts, Jessica Chadwell, Rory Haiber, Jeff Riggs, James Manfredi, Nizar K. Wattad, James McMahan, Mindy Miner, Emily WilsonWilliam Pucilowsky, Carl Gudenius, Frank Page, Elizabeth Crosbie, Courtney Ischinger, Patricia Jenson, Christopher Hahn, Liza Deringer, Mary Elizabeth Williamson, Andy Caradimitropoulo, Cynthia Saunders, Angel Fisher, students of TRDA 130, Emily WilsonLeslie B. Jacobsen, Mary Buckley, Kerry DeVivo, Nathan Garner, Carl Gudenius, Alicia Grayson, Elizabeth Kitsos, Joseph Mills, Stacy Palatt, William Pucilowsky, Bradley Sabelli, Sarah Slifer, Alan Wade, Maida Withers, Stacy Wolf, Judy Annis, Pamela Bentley, Danielle Queen, Mary C. Davis, Judy Annis, Eleanor Miller, Marjorie Mills, Ashton Alvis, Veronica Morrison Dramaturg-Jennifer Connell Movement Coach-Jenna Harju Composer-Jason Ditzian
  - "Summer and Smoke", 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Tennessee Williams (Playwright); Leslie Jacobson (Director); Bradley W. SabelliJean S. RosenthalWilliam PucilowskyDorothy Neumann: composer/performerLeon S. ZiontsMitchell Slater, Deidre Gyr Patterson, Michael Mills, Deidre Lavrakas, Cathy Lee Jones, Jane Beard, Randy Fink, Jeff Most, Donna Birndorf, Lisa Zarowin, George Serletis, Gil Nelson, Paul Washington, Stuart ZamskyDon Russell, John Goetke, Charles Mannheimer, R.Lavine, Jon Newton, D.Neumann. P.Zakutansky, Patricia McGuigan, D.Conway, A.N.Richardson, C.Fishman, P.Dempsey, Ellen Gavin, H.Doster, Howard S. Rahn, L.Zarowin, David Touger, Nancy Weinburg, Vicki Via
  - "Dream of a Common Language" (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - "Into the Woods" (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - "Danceworks", 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Dana Tai Soon Burgess (Director); Maja E WhiteAmanda Edgerton and Ellen WarnerNicholette Routhier, Kristy Shimabukuro, Tommy Parlon, Maida Withers, Mary Tisa, Anthony Gongora, Jennifer NugnetMeggie Baker, Cathryn PaineElizabeth Berk, Carolyn Craig, Jessica Gohs, Michael Gonene, Matthew Krell, Rebecca Lubart, Kendall Mrano, Polly Thibodeau, Amberlee Woods, Aliza Rudavsky, Chirstin Goelz, Pilar del Mazo, Lara Malakoff, Juliana Mascielli, Mollie Straff, Talia MamoneWilliam Pucilowsky, Krstina Hie, Stephen Gray, Jasmine Briggs, Amanda Edgerton, Elizabeth Groth, Natasha Pavlovich, Holly Thomas, Mary Lane, Samantha Schoenholtz, Christina Conley, Marcia Elena LoMonaco, Carrie Kerstein, Aliza Rudavsky, Jennifer GersteinSamantha Schoenholtz, Liz Denniston, Kati Chupasko, Jennifer Caulk, Sarah Halzack, Rebecca Lubart, Natalie Shriber, JJ Kovacevich, Mary Lane, Susanna Brown, Wendell Cooper, Natalie Shriber, Christina Conley, Nicholette Routhier, Kristy Shimabukuro, M Tisa
  - "Juvenilia", 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Wendy MacLeod (Playwright); Elizabeth Kitsos-Kang (Director); Andrew Karlin (Scenic Design)
  - "Merrily We Roll Along", 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Stephen Sondheim and Geroge Furth (Playwrights); Leslie Jacobson (Director)
  - "Shakespeare's Dog", 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Rick Chafe, adapted from the novel by Leone RookeAlan Wade (Director); Samantha Schaeffer (Scenic Design)
  - "Double Bill", 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Halo Wines (Director); Andrew Karlin (Scenic Design)
  - "Paris When It Sizzled", 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Viola Farber, Cunningham Technique, 03/12/1971; Series 5; 1-inch videotape (Film can 1, Reel 1)
  - Viola Farber Repertory, Regional Festival performance, 03/13/1971; Series 5; 1-inch videotape (Film can 2, Reel 2)
  - Regional Festival, Performance 3-4, 03/13/1971; Series 5; 1-inch videotape (Film can 3, Reel 3)
  - Dew Horse, 06/1972; Series 5; 1-inch videotape (Film can 4, Reel 4)
  - Repertory, 07/03/1968; Series 5; 1-inch videotape (Film can 5, Reel 5)
    Scope and Contents
    1) Class practicing 2) Judith Dunn doing the complete piece, #4 solo 3) Class practicing
  - Al Huang, Spring 1969; Series 5; 1-inch videotape. (Film can 6, Reel 6)
  - Ethel Winter Technique Class, Demonstration tape #1, 2, 5, and 6, undated; Series 5; 1-inch videotape. (Film can 7, Reel 7)
  - Judith Dunn Technique Class, 07/01/1968; Series 5; 1-inch videotape. (Film can 8, Reel 8)
  - Don Redlick, Summer Dance Workshop Concert, Part I, 06/21/1973; Series 5; 1/2-inch videotape. (Film can 9, Reel 9)
  - Don Redlick, Summer Dance Workshop Concert, Part II, 06/21/1973; Series 5; 1/2-inch videotape. (Film can 9, Reel 10)
  - Don Redlick, Summer Dance Workshop Concert, Part III, 06/21/1973; Series 5; 1/2-inch videotape. (Film can 9, Reel 11)
    Label on reel: K. Dunham, June 6 1971 and Prez, June 16
  - Beverly Brown [1/2], 10/26/1978; Series 5; 1/2-inch videotape. (Film can 9, Reel 12)
  - Beverly Brown [2/2], 10/26/1978; Series 5; 1/2-inch videotape. (Film can 9, Reel 13)
  - Beverly Brown #2, 06/12/1979; Series 5; 1/2-inch videotape. (Film can 10, Reel 14)
  - Rudy Perez Summer Dance Workshop, "Transit" and "Monumental Exchange", 1971; Series 5; 1/2-inch videotape. (Film can 10, Reel 15)
  - Al Huang Summer Dance Workshop Concert, 06/22/1972; Series 5; 1/2-inch videotape. (Film can 10, Reel 16)
    Part II: "Yu Lan," "A Shadow's Flight," "Hexagrams!!"
  - Guest Artist Sara Rudner in Building J Performance, 30th Birthday (Last 1/2 of tape), undated; Series 5; 1/2-inch videotape. Accompanying note: "Laser is no more seen on tape, only heard." (Film can 10, Reel 17)
  - DanceWorks Fall 2003, 11/19-11/22/2003 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2008, 4/17/08 (Box 3)
  - Moving Forward: Expressions in Contemporary Asian American Dance (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2003, 4/9-4/12/2003 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2005, 4/28/05 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Fall 2005, 11/17/05 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Fall 2005, 11/18/05 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2003, 4/9-4/12/2003 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2003, 4/9-4/12/2003 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2005, 4/28/05 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Fall 2003, 11/19-11/22/2003 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Fall 2003, 11/19-11/22/2003 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Fall 2005, 11/17/05 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2005, 4/28/05 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks 2004, 11/20/04 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Fall 2007, 11/15/07 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2007, 4/26/07 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Fall 2006, 11/16/06 (Box 3)
  - Jacob's Pillow Dance (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2006, 4/28/06 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Fall 2005, November 2005 (Box 3)
  - Spring Dance Concert, 4/1990 (Box 3)
  - Spring Dance Concert, 3/30/89 (Box 3)
  - Fall Dance Concert, 11/13/1991 (Box 3)
  - Spring Dance Concert Opening Night, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Fall Dance Concert, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Spanish Dance Concert, 10/28/1988 (Box 3)
  - GWU Spring Dance Concert, 4/11/87 (Box 3)
  - Spring Dance, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Dance Concert, 4/19/1991 (Box 3)
  - Fall Dance Concert, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Spring Dance Concert, 1995 (Box 3)
  - DanceWorks Spring 2003, 4/9-4/12/2003 (Box 3)
  - Fall Dance Concert, 11/22/1986 (Box 3)
  - Fall Dance Concert, 11/17/1988 (Box 3)
  - Spring Dance Concert, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Spanish Dance Concert, 11/20/1987 (Box 3)
  - Spring Dance Concert, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Dance, through the eye of the TV Camera (Box 4)
  - Spring Dance Concert, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Student Dance Program, 3/28/1981 (Box 4)
  - Erika Thimey: Dance and Conversations (Box 4)
  - Fall Concert, 11/19/1983 (Box 4)
  - AU Fall Concert, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Fall Concert, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Dancing at Lughnasa, Fall, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Maida Withers Dance Construction Company, Utah Spirit Place*Spirit Planet (Box 4)
  - Maida Withers Dance Construction Company: Russian/American Project, Thresholds Crossed, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Dance Performance, 11/19/1993 (Box 4)
  - Maida Withers Dance Construction Company: Aurora/2001: Dance of the Auroras, Fire in the Sky (Box 4)
  - Theater and Dance, 4/16/1993 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Student Concert, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Student Faculty Dance Concert, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
  - Lunatics and Lovers, Act 2, April 1992 (Box 5)
  - Hayfever, Fall 1995 (Box 5)
  - In Good Company, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Cloud 9, Director: Alan Wade, Fall 1993 (Box 5)
  - Night of the Iguana, 11/3/1994 (Box 5)
  - An Improvisation with Katie Duck, Vincent Cacalano and Tristan Honsinger (Box 5)
  - Little Night Music, Spring 1995 (Box 5)
  - Beyond Therapy, Fall 1989 (Box 5)
  - Cabaret, second dress, 2/24/1993 (Box 5)
  - Anything Goes (Box 5)
  - Patience, 6/15/1989 (Box 5)